http://www.safariltd.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Age Range
0-1 (Infant)
1-2 (Toddler)
3-4 (Preschool)
5-6 (Kindergarten)
7+ (Elementary)
Shop All Toys
NEW Mini Blind Packs!
Good Luck Minis
NEW Mini Blind Packs!
Fun Packs
Shop All Minis
Sea Life Animals
Shark, Whales, and More!
Shop All Categories
Toys On Sale!
Privacy Policy
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how Safari Programs, Inc. d/b/a Safari Ltd (“Safari”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) collects, uses, stores, and discloses information, including personally identifiable information and any other information relating to an identified or identifiable person (collectively, the “Personal Information”), of users (each, a “User”, “you”, or “your”) of the Safari website ("Site").
By accessing or using the Site in any way, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your access to and use of the Site is also subject to our Terms and Conditions (“Terms”). If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy or our Terms, please do not use the Site.  By providing Personal Information, and any other information, through the Site, you represent that you have the authority to provide such Personal Information and/or such other information.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us online, by e-mail to website@safariltd.com , or by mail to Safari Ltd®, 5960 Miami Lakes Drive, Miami Lakes, FL 33014.
What Information We Collect
Information you provide
Whenever you register for an account, place an order, fill out a form, subscribe to a newsletter, contact Safari, or interact with social media functionality, certain Personal Information will be requested from you. The requested Personal Information may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, payment information, and details of a request. Additionally, you may decide to provide non-requested information, including Personal Information, through the Site for various reasons, such as to provide suggestions for new products or to obtain assistance from Bernie, the chatbot.
In each instance, collecting this information is necessary for us to fulfill your request. You can always refuse to provide any information, including Personal Information, but please understand that without this requested information, you may be unable to access certain parts of the Site and Safari may be unable to fulfill your request.
Information collected automatically
Whenever you visit the Site, we automatically collect information about your system and your use of the Site, including internet protocol (IP) address, browser name, computer type, operating system, internet service provider, time and length of your visit to the Site, pages you looked at on the Site, PDF files you downloaded through the Site, and the website that may have referred you to our Site. This information is necessary so that we can help diagnose problems with our server(s), administer the Site, analyze trends, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Site, and deliver customized, personalized content.
The Site uses "cookies" to enhance User experience. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the website's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your account, shopping cart, or request. Cookies are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current activity on the Site, which enables us to improve the Site. You may choose to set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do so, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
Non-Personal Information
We collect and create de-identified and aggregated information and other non-Personal Information, which does not identify an individual personally (“Non-Personal Information”).  User agrees that Safari owns without restriction all Non-Personal Information.
How We Use Your Information
Generally
We use your Personal Information only for the purpose you provided such Personal Information.  For instance, the e-mail address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, as well as to respond to inquiries and other requests related to your order.
We use your Personal Information to:
Create and maintain your account;
Create and save orders and wish lists;
Process orders and transactions;
Keep track of your Bernie Bucks;
Respond to your customer service requests and support needs;
Provide you with a tailored experience on the Site;
Administer a promotion, survey, or other Site feature;
Send you newsletters and pertinent information which you have registered for and consented to receive;
Verify your identity and protect Personal Information and other information against unauthorized access, loss, destruction, or alteration;
Send you periodic e-mails related to our products;
Solicit your feedback;
Fulfill your requests;
Improve customer service; and
Enhance functionality of our Site.
Marketing
If you opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive periodic e-mails that may include company news, updates, stories, and product information. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail or you may contact us online or by e-mail to website@safariltd.com.
Non-Personal Information
Because Non-Personal Information cannot be used to personally identify you, we may use such information for any lawful purpose.
How We Store and Protect Your Information
We only store your Personal Information for as long as is necessary to provide you with the Site and your account and fulfill your requests, or as otherwise required by law.  We implement appropriate information processing practices and technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your Personal Information.
The exchange of Personal Information between Users and the Site occurs over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. However, no internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. You should always take special care in deciding what information you send or otherwise make available on the internet, including through this Site.
With Whom We Share Your Personal Information
Generally
We do not sell, trade, rent, share, disclose, or otherwise transfer your Personal Information to any third party, except for sharing your Personal Information with suppliers, website hosting partners, payment processors, and other trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Site and conducting our business, or as otherwise required by law. We may use third party service providers to help us operate the Site, process payments,  store and access Personal Information, perform analytics, and administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. These third party service providers are contractually bound to only process the limited Personal Information we provide them to perform specific tasks at our direction, as necessary to provide the Site and fulfill your requests.
Marketing
We do not sell, trade, rent, share, disclose, or otherwise transfer your Personal Information to any third party for external marketing purposes. However, if you opt-in to our mailing list, we may share your Personal Information for internal marketing purposes with trusted third party partners that assist us in creating and sending Safari-related marketing content to our mailing list. Just as with all third party service providers Safari engages, these third party partners are contractually bound to only process the limited Personal Information we provide them to perform this specific task.
Non-Personal Information
Because Non-Personal Information cannot be used to personally identify you, we may share such information for any lawful purpose.
Third Party Links
Generally
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include links on our Site to other websites not operated or controlled by us. It is also possible that a third party website may include links to our Site without our knowledge or permission.  These third party websites are subject to separate and independent privacy policies and terms and conditions. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content or activities of any of these linked or linking websites.  Inclusion of links to third party websites on our Site does not imply that Safari endorses or has reviewed the third party websites, and inclusion of links to our Site on third party websites does not imply that Safari has knowledge of the links or has given permission.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these third party websites.
Social media features
The Site offers third party social media features, such as the #LoveSafari public board and Bernie’s Backyard, which let you share your creativity on social media platforms with other Users on the Site and allow you to visit and follow Safari on the social media platforms of your choice by clicking on the appropriate social media widget on the Site. When you click on and/or use any of these social media features, your Personal Information will be processed by that social media platform according to the platform’s own privacy policies. The use of such features may enable the sharing of information, including Personal Information, with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with each social media platform. The social media platforms may also collect other information in connection with your use of their features, including your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. For more information about the privacy practices of these social media platforms, please visit each platform’s privacy policy.
External payment processors
In addition to the Site’s internal checkout feature, the Site includes links to third party payment processors, such as PayPal and Google Pay. These external payment services are provided for the convenience of our Users. You do not have to use one of these external payment services to complete your checkout, as you may use our internal checkout feature instead.  When you click a link to one of these external payment processors, you will be directed to that payment processor’s log-in page in order to complete the checkout through that payment processor. Any information you provide once on the payment processor’s webpage is subject to that payment processor’s privacy policies, not Safari’s.  For more information about the privacy practices of these external payment processors, please visit each payment processor’s privacy policy.
How We Handle Children’s Information
While the Site is intended to be accessed and used only by adults 18 years of age or older, we understand that the nature of our business and the content of our Site may lead to children accessing the Site. We are committed to protecting the privacy and safety of all of our Users, especially children, while accessing or using our Site. Accordingly, we take extra steps, including, but not limited to, compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), to make sure children have a safe experience with the Site and their Personal Information is respected and protected at all times.  We also strongly encourage every parent or guardian to take an active role in monitoring their child’s use of the internet and adopting appropriate safeguards, such as device and browser controls and preferences. We consider a child as any person under the age of 18 years old.
We do not intentionally or knowingly collect Personal Information of children without the consent of a parent or legal guardian. If we discover that we have unintentionally or unknowingly collected information from a child in a way that is not in compliance with COPPA, we will delete the information immediately.
In order to prevent unintentional collection of a child’s information without parental/guardian consent, we use age gates to prevent children from accessing sections or features of the Site which request Personal Information. These age gates may be in the form of a pop-up or a checkbox on an online form.  For instance, the shopping cart and checkout features of the Site may only be accessed and used by persons 18 years of age or older. For each browsing session, navigating to the shopping cart or checkout features on the Site requires affirmative confirmation that the User is over the age of 18. If a child, in spite of these safeguards, orders a product through the Site, then the parent or guardian may return the product for a refund according to our refund policy as posted at the time of purchase and we will delete any information of the child immediately.  If you believe your child has placed an order on the Site, please alert us as soon possible by e-mail to website@safariltd.com .
Although the Site is not intended for use by children, children may wish to interact with Safari by filling out the Contact Us form, signing up for our mailing list, posting to social media with #LoveSafari and sharing on the Site, or signing up to become a Safariologist. Each of these features includes an age gate prior to submittal that requests a parent’s or guardian’s e-mail address if the User is a child. We will only use this e-mail address to contact the parent or guardian to explain what feature the child is attempting to access, what information will be collected, how that information will be used, how that information may be shared, and how long we will store that information, and provide the option for the parent or guardian to give or deny consent. In each case, we will not collect the child’s information unless and until we first receive the verifiable consent of the parent or guardian.
In order to obtain verifiable parental or guardian consent, we may: (1) request that the parent or guardian sign a consent form and send it back to us; (2) verify through a payment method; or (3) request that the parent or guardian provide a form of government issued identification.  All information collected for the purpose of obtaining verifiable consent will be promptly deleted upon completion of the verification process.
In the event that a child contacts Safari through e-mail or otherwise, we may collect limited contact information from the child without obtaining parental or guardian consent in order to respond directly to the child on a one-time basis. This limited information will be promptly deleted upon responding to the child’s request.
There may be cases in which Safari is legally obligated to process a child’s Personal Information, even without a parent or guardian’s consent, including to: (1) protect the security or integrity of the Site; (2) take precautions against liability; (3) respond to a judicial process or subpoena; or (4) to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety.
After verifying your identity as parent or legal guardian, you may at any time request, by e-mail to website@safariltd.com , to view the Personal Information we have collected on your child, update or correct the Personal Information, request that the Personal Information be deleted, withdraw your previously granted consent, or refuse to allow further collection or use of the Personal Information.
Your Rights Regarding Your Information
According to the law of certain jurisdictions, you may have the right to request access to your Personal Information, rectification of inaccurate Personal Information, erasure of your Personal Information, restriction of the processing of certain Personal Information, and that your Personal Information be transferred. According to the law of certain jurisdictions, you may also have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information and to withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Information. You can send an e-mail to website@safariltd.com to exercise your rights at any time or write us at:
Safari Ltd
Attn: Personal Information Request
5960 Miami Lakes Dr.
Miami Lakes, FL 33014
If you have a concern about our privacy practices, please contact us using the contact information set forth above, and we will take reasonable steps to address your concern.  According to the law of certain jurisdictions, you may also have the right to make a complaint at any time to a supervisory authority in the European Economic Area.
Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights
Individuals who are residents of California and have provided their Personal Information to us may request information regarding our disclosures, if any, of their Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted in writing at:
Safari Ltd
Attn: Request for California Privacy Information
5960 Miami Lakes Dr.
Miami Lakes, FL 33014
Such requests must include the reference Request for California Privacy Information in the subject line and in the body of the message and must include the e-mail address or mailing address, as applicable, for us to send our response. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted to us if not submitted pursuant to the terms set forth above.
CAN-SPAM Act
We are committed to being compliant with the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (“CAN-SPAM Act”). All e-mails you receive from Safari or through the Site are intended to fully comply with the CAN-SPAM Act.  If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, you can e-mail us at
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Unsolicited Information
This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us or another User through the Site or any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as bulletin boards or forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, claim or demand letters, Digital Millennium Copyright Act notices, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.  However, if any of your Personal Information is included in any Unsolicited Information we will only process that Personal Information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We have the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any time we revise this Privacy Policy, we will update the date at the top of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect your Personal Information. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or your interactions with the Site, please contact us online or at:
Safari LtdSafariltd.com5960 Miami Lakes Dr.
on every purchase.
Wanna Save 10%?
Join and save on your next order!
Explore
Blog & News
Careers
Earn Rewards!
Toys on Sale!
Animals
Dinosaurs
Dragons
Shop All
Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | SitemapCopyright © 2020 Safari Ltd®. All rights reserved.
Login
Close menu
Shop By
Age Range
0-1 (Infant)
1-2 (Toddler)
3-4 (Preschool)
5-6 (Kindergarten)
7+ (Elementary)
NEW Mini Blind Packs!
NEW Mini Blind Packs!
Fun Packs
Shop All Minis
Sea Life Animals
Shark, Whales, and More!
Toys On Sale!
